<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>POKE: What fascinating creatures these are! Mere minutes ago when this planet was submerged, these fish were swimming and playing with such energy, but since the water receded they appear to have transitioned to breathing air, and every single one has ceased its motion.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>OENO: Hypothesis: Sleep in these fish may be triggered by dryness. I theorize that this is their way of sleeping. Melorae shared with me accounts of creatures she encountered in other systems, and a substantial portion of them rest under specific conditions such as darkness. There's no reason why dryness couldn't have a similar effect, in my opinion.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>CLARY: How can you tell that they are breathing? Suppose they are retaining oxygen internally somehow?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>POKE: I can see them moving; it appears that their bodies are slowly rising and falling. They likely posses lungs.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>CLARY: Maybe our own species was not too dissimilar in the past? Personally, I notice that warmth tends to keep me more alert than the cold. It's plausible that our forebears rested during the night when the air cooled and awakened as the warmth of the day emerged.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>OENO: I'm keen on learning about our species' history, but if we aim to meet and inquire with another clan about their knowledge, our priority should be to repair our mortally wounded vessel.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>POKE: They do seem very much asleep, I wonder how long it takes for them to wake up after the water starts flooding again?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
</NomaiObject>